CARSON KEY

Software Engineer

Portfolio: https://carsonkey.dev/ Bend, Oregon carson@key.family

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/carson-key-720a04b6/ Github: https://github.com/Carson-Key/

To gain more experience working on large scale and small scale projects alike to advance my personal growth and knowledge. Appling experience and knowledge gained to a full-time career in Software Engineering.

Professional Experience

June 2021 - Present

Temp Tech Consultant

Oregon State University-Cascades, Bend, Oregon

- Helping prepare all classrooms for a return to in person classes (this was in 2021, durning the pandemic)
- Helping train and orientate two new hires to the Cascades team
- Getting all computers imaged ready for the school year, this ranged form faculty computers to lab machines
- Developing miscellaneous software for the Cascades IT team
- Developing a React based dashboard for the director of OSU main campus at Corvallis to display statuses of various products

February 2018 -June 2021 IT Student Worker

Oregon State University-Cascades, Bend, Oregon

- · Collect data and modify configs on various servers
- Troubleshoot and fix user technology issues which ranged from faculty/staff compiters to classroom computers
- Preping all technology ready for the school year
- · Odd tech II tasks

July 2019 - January 2020

Developer Intern

Redhawk Network Security, LLC, Bend, Oregon

- Maintain legacy software
- PHP development
- Add new features to legacy code
- Start development on a React based account creation wizard

June 2018 -

September 2018

Developer Intern

CBT Nuggets, Bend, Oregon

- Developing a React based website to be used in the QA engineer interview process
- Developing a React based dashboard addon to display test automation statistics

References

 $\textbf{Tania Mahood} \mid \mathsf{Director} \ \mathsf{of} \ \mathsf{IT} \ \mathsf{at} \ \mathsf{OSU} \ \mathsf{-Cascades}$

Evan Randall | Equipment Specialist at OSU-Cascades

Tyler Hardison | CTO at Redhawk Network Security

Ryan Sullivan | Team Leader/QA Engineer at Cbr Nuggets

Kathie Quick | Math Department Head and CS Teacher at Summit High School

Sarah Warsow | Activities Director at Summit High School

 $\textbf{Greig Thompson} \ | \ \mathsf{AP} \ \mathsf{CS} \ \mathsf{and} \ \mathsf{Science} \ \mathsf{Teacher} \ \mathsf{at} \ \mathsf{Summit} \ \mathsf{High} \ \mathsf{School}$

Education

Bachelor of Science in Software

Oregon State University-Cascades at Bend, Oregon | September 2017 - June 2021

High School Honors Diploma Summit High School at Bend, Oregon | 2013 - 2017

Key Skills

Leadership

Troubleshooting/Debugging

Swift Programming Language

React

Web Development

rull Stack

Javascript

Node.js

Code Design (Software Engineering)

Ability to Learn New Skills